

Paweł Lorencowicz

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

During last three years I worked in the design center contributing to big international projects. Utilising good communication skills, I maintained successful working relationships with both internal and external staff. As a highly-motivated and results orientated I am looking to secure a position, where I can develop current skillset further.

CONTACT ME

- +48 725 200 007
- ☑ p.lorencowicz@gmail.com
- ◀ Warszawa, Poland
- github.com/lor3k
- in linkedin.com/in/plorencowicz

EDUCATION

- → Front-End full-time course infoShare Academy

 Nov 2017 Feb 2018
- Warsaw University of Technology
 Transportation and Highway Engineering
 2013 2015
- Warsaw University of Technology Engineer's degree, Civil Engineering 2008 – 2013

EXPERIENCE

- Road Designer Assistant

 Multiconsult

 May 2015 Sep 2017
- Road Designer Assistant AECOM Feb 2015 – May 2015
- Construction Engineer STRABAG Jul 2013 – Sep 2013

SKILLS

| | JavaScript ES6 | MacOS |
|---|----------------|--------|
| | React.js | Linux |
| _ | Doduyis | ۸ aila |

HTML5 — AutoCAD

CSS3 Photoshop

SASS Inkscape

Bootstrap 📼 MathCAD

■ GIT ■ PHP
■ RWD ■ mvS

RWD **---** mySQL Webpack **---** Babel

REST API 🗩 Node.js

LANGUAGES

English C1 German B1 Norwegian A1

HOBBIES

technologies, cycling, sailing, climbing, travelling

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997 roku o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity: Dz. U. z 2002r. Nr 101, poz. 926 ze zm.).